hello everyone this is kangsha
gangapuram and you're watching hibis
news otis made to move communities
global challenge recognizes students
representing otis india for their
innovative mobility solutions torrent
power limited has under the securities
purchase agreement spa with sky power
south east asia
three investments limited and sky power
south east asia holding two limiteds and
sunshakti solar power project private
limited spv completed the transaction of
acquisition of hundred percent
securities of the spv the spv operates a
50-megawatt solar power plant in the
state of telangana the long-term power
purchase agreement ppa for the project
is when northern power distribution
company of telangana limited
npdctl for a period of over 25 years at
a fixed traffic of approx rupees 5.35
per kwh with remaining useful life of
approx 20 years enterprise value for
this acquisition is approx 416 crores
consequent to closing adjustments
torrent power the integrated power
utility of the diversified torrent with
group revenues of approx 22 500 cr and a
market cap of 70 000 crores is one of
the largest companies in the country
power sector with the presence across
the entire power value chain of
generations transmission and
distributions signing off keep watching
highways news
you